picosong.com 2019-10-24

# Privacy Policy - picosong

## Privacy Policy:

It is picosong’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, picosong collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. picosong’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how picosong’s visitors use its website. From time to time, picosong may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

picosong also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. picosong does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to picosong’s website choose to interact with picosong in ways that require picosong to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that picosong gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account to provide a username and email address. In each case, picosong collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with picosong. picosong does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

picosong may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. For instance, picosong may monitor the most popular pages on the picosong site. picosong may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, picosong does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

picosong discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on picosong’s behalf or to provide services available at picosong’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using picosong’s website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. picosong will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, picosong discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when picosong believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of picosong, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an picosong website and have supplied your email address, picosong may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with picosong and our products. We primarily use our product blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. picosong takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. picosong uses cookies to help picosong identify and track visitors, their usage of picosong website, and their website access preferences. picosong visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using picosong’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of picosong’s website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Ads

Ads appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by picosong and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, picosong may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in picosong’s sole discretion. picosong encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

* * *

picosong's Privacy Policy was adapted from [Wordpress.com](https://www.wordpress.com/) and [Automattic](https://www.automattic.com/)'s Privacy Policy and is available under a **Creative Commons Sharealike** license. picosong thanks them very much for sharing their policy.
